- [Neal] Are you back for dinner?
- I should be.
Could get used
to this nine-to-five thing.
[sighs]
Don't.
♪ dramatic music ♪
- We good?
- [Randy] You're good.
Aleksi Yurimov.
I'm sorry. I'm not up
on my Russian spies.
You'd be taking Putin's queen
off the chessboard.
Ever been to Ukraine?
[gunfire]
- [dogs bark]
- [soldiers scream]
Never seen that shit.
[Cody]
Blow it.
[soldiers shout in distance]
[Joe]
Gray beard
- right in front of you.
- [Cody] Dump the rest.
[Aleksi grunts]
[knock on door]
Can I help you?
We're with state police.
You're not the police.
[Joe groans]
I need FBI to my house
right now.
I'm blown.
[grunts]
I'm blackjacked!
[tires screech]
- Joe?
- No!
- [man shouts]
- [Joe screams]
[Joe panting]
♪ low. tense music ♪
[vehicle door opens]
[door closes]
[door creaks. closes]
[panting]
- [Joe yelling]
- [shouting in Russian]
[Joe shrieking]
- [grunting]
- [Joe groaning]
No more fight.
[Joe panting]
Try again
and the hurt will be bad.
[grunts]
[panting]
No.
[groans]
- [speaking Russian]
- [yells]
[grunts]
[panting]
[grunting]
[groans]
♪
[groaning]
[grunts. panting]
[grunts. groans]
[panting]
[muttering in Russian]
[Joe panting]
[yells]
[grunting]
- [speaks Russian]
- [panting]
I don't wear a locator.
Of course you wear a locator.
You're a spy.
- You have implant.
- [Joe] We don't do that.
- Everyone does that.
- [panting]
Not us.
[man]
We'll see.
I know all the hiding places.
- [grunts]
- [grunts. whimpers]
[panting]
[grunts. panting]
[groaning]
[man speaks Russian]
[grunting]
[panting. grunting]
[panting]
Open mouth.
[grunts. panting]
♪
[man breathing heavily]
[flashlight clicks]
Where is it?
I told you
we don't wear locators.
If you don't tell me.
I just keep looking.
We don't use them.
Airport scanners pick them up.
I'll tear you in half
to find it.
[Joe breathing heavily]
♪
[grunts softly]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
No! Oh!
- [clanging]
- [breathing heavily]
♪
[clinking]
- Roll her over.
- [yells]
[yells. panting]
[panting]
Wait.
Okay.
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
Big toe. left foot.
[clanking]
[shudders]
[clacks]
♪
[groaning. panting]
[grunts. panting]
[man speaks Russian]
[grunting]
[panting]
[speaks Russian]
Get dressed.
♪
[grunts]
[panting]
♪ low. percussive music ♪
Talon. this is Roadrunner.
We are three mikes to target.
- Over.
- [Talon] Roger. Roadrunner.
We see Raven still on site.
- Over.
- Roger that.
I read the same. Over.
Two minutes!
Drop-off at release point one.
Bravo at release point two.
Then rally at the south edge
of property for exfil.
Same if exfil's hot?
Won't be hot.
Killing every one
of these motherfuckers.
[tires screech]
[tires screeching]
♪
Get inside.
Close and lock the door.
[engine revving]
♪
- With you.
- [revving]
♪
[grunts]
♪ low. tense music ♪
On you.
♪
[click]
[clacking]
♪
- [Tucker] Clear.
- [Tex] Clear.
♪
♪ dramatic. haunting music ♪
- [line ringing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Westfield]
Give me good news.
I don't have any.
They found the locator.
That's all they found.
Left it behind?
Mm-hmm.
Overplaying their hand a bit.
Maybe. Maybe it's their way
of saying we overplayed ours.
[sighs]
You need to find me
the common denominator
in this mess.
May I make a request?
- Sure.
- Call in our team from Peary.
That's a pretty blunt instrument
stateside. Kaitlyn.
You have her QRF.
You have her HRT standing by.
Everybody breaks. Byron.
You know that.
And when she breaks.
who knows what spills out?
I'll have 'em to you
in six hours.
You shake that tree
until you find her.
Yes. sir.
With both fucking hands.
Don't leave a mess.
We'll clean as we go.
♪ low. somber music ♪
[starts engine]
[gearshift clicks]
♪
[Kate]
Dad. what are you doing?
Uh. I forgot something.
Won't take a second.
I'll be right back.
[door shuts]
♪ low. tense music ♪
[door opens]
[door shuts]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Neal panting]
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
- Neal. Neal.
- Kaitlyn.
- Yes. Walk with me. Walk with...
- No. What? What? What?!
What happened to my wife?!
[quietly]
Shut the fuck up.
The neighbors are watching.
There has been an incident.
which we are solving.
Your wife is alive. okay?
She's gonna stay that way.
Is that all you got for me.
Kaitlyn?
I'm sure you've discussed this.
Worst-case scenarios.
Is that what this is?
Worst-case scenario?
When I know more.
you'll know more.
What do I tell my kids?
[sniffs]
Nothing. Okay?
Nothing? I have
to drive them to school.
And when I back out
of that driveway
and they see their mother's
battered fucking car
- right there...
- I'll take care of the car.
You have 90 seconds.
♪
[exhales]
Uh. I forgot my wallet.
I'm sorry.
You do know
you can keep everything
on your phone now. Dad.
You don't need a wallet.
[Neal]
You are right.
Uh. looks like they got the road
shut down for something.
We get to take the long way
to school today.
Okay. then can you write me
a note?
'Cause I'm gonna be late.
Me. too. Dad.
Two notes. coming up.
♪
♪ low. somber music ♪
[insects buzzing]
[sighs]
[helicopter whirring past]
[singsongy]
Honey. I'm home.
No supper?
Woman...
...when I come home
from a hard day's work...
...I expect a fucking meal
on the fucking table.
Supper...
- ...on the table.
- [Josie] I just figured
we'd skip straight to dessert.
Happy birthday.
It's not my birthday.
It's somebody's birthday.
And you should be happy
about that.
Happy birthday. somebody.
♪ low. gentle music ♪
Mm.
[laughs]
Oh. yeah?
[chuckling]
Mmm.
I'm gonna have to shower.
I haven't bathed in a week.
I'm dressed for a bath.
Yes. you are.
♪
Thank God
I don't have a foot fetish.
[water splashes]
Man.
War is hell on feet.
[Cruz chuckles softly]
How'd it go?
We all made it home.
So it went good?
[sighs]
It was successful.
I wouldn't say it was good.
What we do...
...it's gonna be obsolete
in 30 years.
Ukraine stopped
a 3.5-million-man army
dead in its tracks... fucking...
$90 drones from Amazon.
What in the fuck are we fighting
the next war with?
You know. Einstein was asked
what weapons we'd use
in World War III.
He said he had no idea. but
he knew what weapons we'd use
in World War IV.
Sticks.
Sticks?
He's wrong.
Bunch of machines fight
the next one.
they won't even ask
our permission.
That one's clean.
[Josie]
I know.
Just rubbing it
for good luck now.
I think...
maybe...
...it's my turn.
- Well. that's not my foot.
- No.
♪
Where do you want to start?
[breathing heavily]
[phone ringing. buzzing]
[Cruz]
Fuck.
Shit. I just got home.
Every fucking time.
[buzzing. ringing continues]
All I had to do
was think about sex.
and I'm getting fucking
called for duty.
Fuck me.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
[car door closes]
[sighs]
Let me have it.
Well. this one
and the one in the yard
rang the doorbell.
identified themselves as PD.
asked Joe to step outside.
did not provide ID when asked.
She closed the door. they kicked
it in and they rushed her.
And you can see how well
that turned out for them.
- ID?
- Virginia driver's licenses.
NSA says passports are Romanian.
Both men have Belarus passports
under different names.
Where is she?
Sitting on the stairs.
A little gun-shy
of all the windows right now.
Well. we need to move her
and her family.
House at the farm?
Give me options.
- [line ringing]
- Hey.
[Meade]
Romanian passports.
but NSA says Belarus nationals.
which means Russian SVR.
They attempted to force entry
through the front door.
posing as state police officers
without ID.
Amateurs.
- It doesn't make sense.
- No.
but pretty convenient timing.
given that we do a snatch
and they show up
at our front door.
Let's assume they have
eyes and ears on location.
You come in
and we'll talk about it.
And Kaitlyn?
- Bring me the thinkers.
- Yeah.
♪
[sighs]
You've had quite the weekend.
This one just won't end.
[sighs] In front of my family.
My fucking family.
There's reckless.
and then there's "What the fuck?
- What was that?"
- We'll talk about this
- in the office. Let's go.
- No.
- I'm not leaving my family.
- Your team is en route.
They're gonna secure
your family.
take them somewhere safe.
Let's go.
There's eyes everywhere.
- Come on.
- Let me say goodbye.
Let's go.
No. of course.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
We got 'em. boss.
Y'all sweep the back?
Sweep it for what?
Perps are laying
in the front yard.
What do you think's in the back?
[Two Cups scoffs]
♪ eerie. dark music ♪
♪
Does any of this shit
make sense?
Not even a little.
So. let's just say
they were Russian SSD.
and they knock
on the front fucking door?
No fucking way.
- They clearly knew who she was.
- What if they didn't?
Then what the fuck
were they doing here?
[Randy] I'm not saying
the bosses didn't know.
What if we just took
a really shiny penny?
Now look
what that accomplished. huh?
All of us. whole gang.
standing out in the open.
Gonna get some high ground.
Ears on.
♪ fast. suspenseful music ♪
[exhales]
♪
[Tucker]
Mm-hmm.
Mm...
♪ tense. suspenseful music ♪
Spotter identified:
rooftop. far side street.
three houses to the northeast.
Don't wait for me.
♪
[dog yapping]
- Let's go past it two houses.
- Yep.
[Randy]
On you.
♪
[dog barking]
- [man] Hey!
- FBI. Get inside.
- Do not come out.
- Should I call 911?
We are 911. Get the fuck inside.
[door closes]
♪
You got him?
[Two Cups]
Uh. yep.
I see that fucker.
- How you want to do this?
- Well.
let's assume he's not alone.
He's got cover and exfil.
- [man 2] Scooter!
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Scooter? [kissing]
[Randy]
Tucker. you got a mover
- on your one o'clock.
- Scooter. here!
Yep. 50 meters and closing.
[Two Cups]
Wait till he's locked on.
[Randy]
Wait. wait.
He's locked.
♪ fast. pulsing music ♪
You see a little dog?
A little short-haired terrier?
FBI? Everything okay?
No. I wouldn't say so.
What happened?
[grunting]
[choking]
[panting]
The spotter is down.
What happened?
♪ tense. suspenseful music ♪
Bobby. we got two PUCs
at our location.
But we still don't have
the driver.
How do you know
there's a driver?
There'd be a driver
if we were doing it.
Yeah. well. we are stuck here
until you find him.
Give me the hat.
[zips bag]
I'm gonna try and draw him out.
♪
[engine starts]
[coughs]
[vehicle approaching]
[loud gunshot]
[Charlie screams]
Oh. no. what is that?
- Hey. guys. we good?
- Boss. let me in there.
- Randy. are we good?
- [Neal] "Are we go..."
Can someone tell me what
the fuck is happening. please?
Yeah. we're good. Driver's down.
Badges out. boys.
The whole world's coming.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
FBI.
Got one down here.
two in the back.
♪
[phone buzzing]
[grunts softly]
It's my team.
We must assume
they have your phone.
assume they have everything.
So just...
[sighs]
[phone buzzes repeatedly]
Get them back.
[phone buzzing]
Hey. boss. we got to...
This phone is no good.
Call mine.
Understood.
[sighs]
- [phone buzzing]
- What?
We got overwatch on the scene.
There's a driver
and two spotters.
The driver is down.
We're holding on
to the two spotters.
FBI wants to know
where you want 'em.
[sighs]
I'll advise direct to command.
Roger that.
♪ slow. somber music ♪
[sighs]
[line ringing]
Hey. they had
surveillance on site.
A team. One is KIA.
two are in custody.
Yeah.
Uh-huh. en route.
[exhales]
Interesting night.
[scoffs]
Have you figured out
the plan yet?
They only missed it
by five or ten minutes.
If I would have taken a shower
instead of pouring myself
a drink.
which is what I do normally...
[sniffles]
...every other time
I come home...
That's why
they didn't have badges.
Nobody was supposed to answer
the fucking door.
They've been on me. Kaitlyn.
for a while.
- A long while.
- I still don't see a plan.
The plan was to kill me.
then kill my family.
then see who bothers to show up
so they know who to kill next.
Nobody plays like that
over here. Joe.
Really? Then I guess
we're the unluckiest
fucking people in D.C.
We die jogging.
We get carjacked at 6 a.m.
on a fucking Monday.
We drown in three feet of water.
They're contract agents.
- [sighs]
- You are a senior case officer.
You're untouchable.
especially within our borders.
Because if you aren't.
the whole world knows
it's open fucking season
on every asset they have
wherever we find them.
I'm feeling pretty fair game
at the moment.
You know who else
feels like fair game?
My soon-to-be ex-husband
and my traumatized daughters.
They came into my home.
My fucking home.
There's no hiding it now.
My kids saw me do it.
They know what I am.
They should be proud
of what you did.
You ever kill someone
in front of your children?
That's how they felt?
They should be proud?
All right. about 20 minutes
from the office. so...
that's gonna be how long you
have to feel sorry for yourself.
You understand?
This isn't the end of a fight.
this is the start of one.
whether you want a fight or not.
because they sure as hell
want a fight with you.
[inhales sharply]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [gentle music playing]
[Hollar]
The issue we have is coming back
from 12 years of inactivity.
We have skeleton resources
in Venezuela.
we've been passive in Geneva.
so fish on the hook is the goal.
[Davis] Let's discuss
the threat of Venezuela.
It's a third world country
on the brink of...
[Hollar] Venezuela is sitting
on the largest
proven oil reserves
in the world.
More than UAE. more than
the Saudis. more than us.
If it was Chevron pumping it
out of the ground
instead of
their corrupt government.
they would dominate the market.
If the Russians
or. God forbid. the Chinese...
[Midvale]
Won't be the Russians.
Iran would see that
as a betrayal.
I can't believe he has the nerve
to dine here tonight.
Doesn't seem odd to you?
Well. it's brazen.
but that's a Russian for you.
Because he thinks
they hold enough chips to trade.
What he doesn't know is.
I just took his chips.
Excuse me.
[scrapes loudly]
What are we drinking?
A 1979 Chateau Lafayette.
- Mm.
- Wine and furniture
are the only two things
the French do well.
- Oh. I don't know...
- But they do them very well.
It's all sauces
to hide the rotting meat.
Their food...
...is like their women.
They all stink without perfume.
Yeah. well.
maybe if they'd have killed
20 million men in 50 years
like you guys.
they could have improved
their herd's aroma. huh?
They didn't have
20 million to spare.
There's a line. Byron.
and you crossed it.
And now there is no line.
Oh. well. you are on
the wrong side of the Atlantic
to be making the rules.
We make the rules here.
And for you.
we're making new ones.
We know what you took...
...we know who took it
and who took it with her.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
[clears throat]
You're not down two.
You're down five.
And the two
that are still breathing.
they're en route to somewhere
where no one is going
to hear them scream
when they don't answer
the questions that we ask.
You have no intel.
You have no surveillance.
What you need to do now
is decide who from your embassy
that we're deporting tomorrow.
because I will clean
your fucking office out.
Do you understand me?
You have no play except
to sit here and suck on it.
Or...
you can pull your troops
out of Eastern Ukraine.
- Ah.
- Better for you. right?
Blame everything on us.
wipe some of that egg
off your face
from the ass-whupping
you've been taking
for the last few years?
What do you want?
Want?
To trade?
Oh. gee. Um...
I don't know.
I mean. you already gave us
our weed-vaping
basketball player back.
I'd say we're pretty good.
- We have your marine.
- Mm-hmm. Yes. you do.
Journalist?
One of those two. yeah.
Iran has one as well.
I'm aware.
So. I think we can
work something out.
No. Not looking
for a trade. Maxim.
Then why are you sitting
at my table?
Because you targeted
a State Department official
on U.S. soil. you motherfucker.
You're about to learn
how long our fingers are.
All this shit
tastes the same to me.
You're not a connoisseur. Maxim.
You're a sucker.
You don't have him.
I don't have one. I have two.
That we pulled off a roof
in fucking Fairfax.
And there is not
a goddamn thing in the world
that I'd trade for 'em.
And once we have wrung
every ounce
of information out of them.
we're gonna feed him
to the feral hogs at Gitmo.
I'll send you some bacon.
And that's a fucking promise.
You know what? I'm gonna
make you another promise.
You tried to touch us here?
[scoffs]
It's a two-way street. buddy.
[chair scrapes]
♪
♪ fast. suspenseful music ♪
[faint radio chatter]
♪
[engine starts]
[vehicle door closes]
♪
- Hey. Hey.
- Hmm?
- Hang in there.
- Yeah. yeah.
Debrief...
and you're home.
- Where's home?
- Camp Peary.
Your family's en route.
It's. uh... it's a nice house.
Last resident was a four-star.
You know how those guys
like to live.
On base?
- Yeah.
- [door opens]
Oh. shit.
Evening. sir.
Goddamn it.
When I write my memoirs.
my lack of sleep is gonna
dominate the narrative.
[Meade chuckles]
[Mullins]
Family okay. Joe?
Yes. sir.
You okay?
Well...
my definition of "okay"
keeps changing. sir.
It comes with the job.
Someday.
you're gonna move to a desk.
Station chief. maybe.
It's time.
Then all of these obstacles
and shit that you've overcome
will be the reason
people don't argue
with your recommendations...
...because your understanding
of the consequences
is not theoretical.
No.
- Mm.
- It is not. sir.
Now. let's talk about
the future later.
Right now.
let's talk about your present.
♪ slow. dark music ♪
How was she made?
We don't know.
Most likely a double in Ukraine.
If they knew why she was there.
the attempt
would have been far
more sophisticated.
They sent low-level
Belarus contract agents
that they didn't care
about losing.
It was. um. it was a probe
more than anything else.
They knew she was in-country.
they know
Yurimov has been taken.
but I don't think
that they've connected the two.
Well. they knew something.
otherwise they wouldn't have
- knocked on her front door.
- No. they wouldn't have.
They would have taken her
like we took him.
Do they think she's involved
in the operation?
I'm sure.
Do they think
he's in our possession?
No. because if they did.
I mean. their reaction would
have been very. very different.
[knock at door]
Is there coffee?
[Meade]
There is.
[liquid pouring]
I was on my fourth glass
of champagne.
so I am going
to need information
delivered in very brief.
very precise phrases.
- Duly noted.
- [knock at door]
You up to speed. ma'am?
I read the action report
on the way over.
Assuming nothing else
has happened...
Byron?
Sir.
You want to give us
a timeline to present?
Sure. Um...
March 4.
a Ukrainian double agent
made contact
with a senior case officer
with information on the location
of Aleksi Yurimov.
Joe was given the assignment.
alongside that case officer.
to apprehend Yurimov. which
we achieved Friday. March 14.
Yurimov is currently being held
at our facility in Jordan
and awaiting transport to Gitmo.
And. depending on
POTUS's position.
either held there indefinitely
or transferred back here
to stand trial
for war crimes against humanity.
[Mason]
Doesn't that require
a U.N. tribunal?
No. We can take the position
that since we have
American citizens
serving observe-and-advise
functions in Ukraine.
that those crimes
are punishable here
because our citizens
are subject to those crimes.
You know. we can also prosecute
for the Wagner Group attacks
against our forces in Syria.
We good?
May I proceed?
By all means.
Upon returning home.
Joe was approached
at her residence by two Belarus
contract agents for Russian SSD.
They attempted to force entry.
Joe neutralized both threats.
Her SRT unit found
an observation team
at the incident site.
They neutralized one.
We're holding the other two
at Langley.
Observation team.
Belarus agents as well?
One American citizen.
two Russian nationals
with green cards.
Assuming the American citizen
is from Russia as well?
[Westfield]
Born in Russia.
moved here in '07. uh.
gained U.S. citizenship in 2016.
Okay. so. sleepers.
- Correct.
- [Mullins] But do we have
any idea how Joe was ID'd?
We have assumptions.
Uh. their presence at Boryspil
is likely extensive.
be it paid informants
who work at the airport
or even
the Ukrainian military itself.
But though brief.
moving from plane to vehicle
at Boryspil
is the likeliest place
that Russian intelligence
could get a visual.
It would seem far more likely
that they identified her
- during the operation. to me.
- [Joe] No one on that side
survived the operation
to identify me. sir.
What about video surveillance?
Satellite imagery?
I was wearing a helmet. glasses.
Those items make
visual referencing impossible.
[Westfield] We don't believe
that she was compromised
at the FOB outside of Pokrovsk.
Likewise. we don't believe
that they have any knowledge
of our direct involvement
in the operation.
If so. they would have
aggressively sought out
our exfil. they'd have
neutralized the base.
Their... their reaction would
have been completely different.
As it were. it is likely
that they were aware
of the capture
until after Joe was stateside.
Or en route. anyway.
[Mason]
So. a fluke.
Video surveillance picks her up
at the airport
and A.I. cross-references
- a library of images.
- Correct.
I mean. they have
incomplete data hauls
from the Shadow Brokers
attack in '17.
The SolarWinds attack in 2020.
They had her picture.
they had her listing
as a State Department official
and now an image
placing her in Ukraine.
Look. if they knew that
she was Special Activities.
they'd have never knocked
on that front door.
May I speak?
Go ahead. Joe.
I've been everywhere. doing...
[chuckles]
[sighs]
They've had ample opportunity
to make me.
and they never have.
Then we meet
a Ukrainian double agent
who. unsolicited.
offers us a giant prize.
Two weeks later.
we have the prize.
and now you have contract agents
and SSD knocking on doors
and climbing rooftops
in some neighborhood in Fairfax.
Occam's razor theorizes
that the solution
with the least amount
of variables
is most likely the answer.
and the least amount
of variables here
is the agent from Ukraine.
She hooked us.
My guess is Yurimov is still
on the Russian front.
and we're sitting on some actor
from the fucking
Mossovet Theatre.
Sorry.
It's been a very long day.
a very long week.
- I haven't slept. so...
- Oh. you're fine.
- Sorry. [clears throat]
- I am looking into
that possibility as we speak.
[phone buzzing]
[Bobby sighs softly]
Yep.
We're en route to...
Oh. no. no. no. We can't divert.
Got Joe's family with me.
You get by with two?
[sighs]
All right.
I'll send them your way.
- Pull over.
- What's going on?
♪ slow. dark music ♪
- Everything's fine.
- If it's fine.
why are we stopping?
[car door closes]
- We good?
- Yeah. I need you and Cruz
to head to Kyle.
We'll give you the location.
The rest of you guys
are with me.
What about all our shit
in the back?
You're gonna cram all your shit
in the Suburban just like
it's a fucking Humvee.
Come on. let's go.
[SUV doors closing]
Welcome to black side.
♪
How are you doing?
[scoffs]
I'm. uh.
pretty fucking not okay.
- Kate.
- I'm fucking not okay. either.
- Charlie.
- [chuckles] Yeah. Good kids.
Hey.
You work with my wife?
I asked you a question.
Do you work with my wife?
You're gonna have to ask
your wife those questions. sir.
We can't answer 'em.
Just did.
["Us" by The Movement playing]
[crowd chatter]
[laughter]
♪ Did you believe in us ♪
♪ Did you believe in trust... ♪
I'll be back.
I'm going to powder my nose.
I have powder for your nose
if you'd like some.
- Well. the night is young.
- [chuckles]
Are you crazy?
You're going to get me killed.
The whole world is in here.
Meet me outside.
Not possible.
[scoffs]
Meet me outside...
...or I'll fucking
drag you outside.
You understand?
Five minutes.
♪ Us ♪
[siren wailing in distance]
Wasn't that
the Secretary of Energy?
You guys running low
on oil or something?
Listen. you can't
show up here. okay?
Everyone in that room is working
and watching and learning.
Well. we got a lot
to talk about.
Then we set a meeting
and we plan it.
I tried that.
but your number ain't working.
Yeah. 'cause I got a new one.
I'll get it to you.
This is my ride.
I'll get it to you tomorrow.
Well. what do you know?
It is tomorrow.
[grunts]
Ow! [gasping]
♪ fast. suspenseful music ♪
Wow. you're really...
[cries out]
[whimpers]
[Kyle] In case you haven't
already figured it out...
[gasping softly]
...you got a lot
of explaining to do.
You gonna sit there all night?
Is that your job?
It's my job tonight.
To keep you safe.
I can sit outside the door
if you want.
but I'm a warrior.
I'd rather stay close.
Yeah. I-I want you close.
You got it.
So. do you...
you. like. know karate
or something?
Then how are you gonna
protect us?
Don't worry. Karate don't want
to run into me.
You got a gun?
Well. I guess that beats karate.
Every time. kiddo.
♪ slow. somber music ♪
♪
[Joe scoffs]
Fucking generals.
- Hey. boss.
- [door closes]
Kids are asleep.
Your husband is. um...
There's a bar down the hall.
♪ slow. somber music ♪
I can't see your eyes.
Come closer.
[crying]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Come here. Come here.
I'm so sorry.
♪ somber. emotional music ♪
♪